export const quidaxData = {
  "data": [
    {
      "quesId": 1,
      "question": "What year was Quidax founded?",
      "options": ["2015", "2016", "2018", "2017"],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "quesId": 2,
      "question": "Which accelerator program did Quidax join in 2020?",
      "options": ["Y Combinator", "Techstars", "Seedcamp", "500 Startups"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "quesId": 3,
      "question": "What is the primary service Quidax provides?",
      "options": ["E-commerce platform", " Stock trading", "Payment processing", " Cryptocurrency exchange"],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "quesId": 4,
      "question": "What is the name of Quidax's native token?",
      "options": ["QDX", "QDAX", "QTX", "QUX"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "quesId": 5,
      "question": "As of the latest update, how many countries does Quidax serve?",
      "options": ["30", "50", "72", "100"],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "quesId": 6,
      "question": "What was a significant challenge Quidax faced when starting out?",
      "options": ["Lack of customers", "Regulatory hurdles", "Liquidity problems", "High competition"],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "quesId": 7,
      "question": "Which company did Quidax help with liquidity issues?",
      "options": ["Trove", "Blueloop", "Buycoins",  "Flux"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "quesId": 8,
      "question": "What major event in 2021 impacted Quidax and other Nigerian crypto startups?",
      "options": ["Global financial crisis", "CBN's crypto ban", "Introduction of new tax laws", "Market saturation"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "quesId": 9,
        "question": "What language options is Quidax planning to add for better reach in Africa?",
        "options": ["French and Portuguese", "French and Swahili", "Spanish and Arabic", "German and Italian"],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "quesId": 10,
        "question": "What volume of transactions has Quidax processed so far?",
        "options": ["$1 billion", "$2 billion", "$3.2 billion", "$5 billion"],
        "answer": 2
    }
]
}
  